itsaboutiphone.co.uk 2014-06-22

# privacy « iPhone Application Reviews | iPhone Latest News | iPhone Latest Reviews | iPhone Accessories

We care about your privacy, this is why itsaboutiphone.co.uk has its comprehensive privacy policy aimed at securing the information you share. We appreciate and regard your trust in us. Kindly go through the below section which describes our privacy policy in detail.

## Personal Information Control

Whatever information you share on itsaboutiphone.co.uk is controlled generally by the company.

1.1) The term ‘Personal Data (information)’ refers to any data that identifies you and your account. You solely agree that all the personal data you provide is true in all aspects. You further agree that you would notify us regarding any change in your personal information within itsaboutiphone.co.uk domain. All your personal data is dealt in compliance with recent UK legislation for data protection. Kindly note that this privacy policy applies only to the internet domain of itsaboutiphone.co.uk and the administration is not responsible for other organization (websites) to which we link directly or indirectly.

1.2) All the personal data collected, processed and stored in itsaboutiphone.co.uk is solely for the service providing and other principles mentioned in the privacy policy.

1.3) We shall send you notifications regarding new products, services, and publications which might interest you through email and text messages, only if you have granted us the permission to do so.

1.4) All the personal data collected about your service usage on itsaboutiphone.co.uk is to cater your needs. The data anonymity shall be maintained in all cases. However, the data shall be unveiled on an anonymous basis which would not identify you in any way.

1.5) We shall gather your personal data regarding any transaction you make with us. However, this sort of critical personal data shall only be shared with third party if there is a need to assist you in the respective transaction. In the same regard, we shall let you know about any product or service that might interest you.

1.6) If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy and the management, processing and protection of your personal data and your rights regarding this agreement you can contact us on [privacy@itsaboutiphone.co.uk](mailto:privacy@itsaboutiphone.co.uk).

1.7) itsaboutiphone.co.uk has the right to disclose your personal data to conform any legal requirement and to comply with a legal process, protect and defend the rights of the web domain. This further enforces the online agreement to protect the interests of the accounts holders of the website. All these actions shall only be performed in the good faith and only if necessary.

****1.8)** **Cookies****

1.       The term ‘cookies’ refer to the small text file that websites use to store use information. This file remains in user hard disk and contains your preferences, like the record of the pages you visits and tends to enhance your search experience by using it for next time.

2.       The cookies only store your choices (clicks) while you visit a website. For instance the website cannot obtain your email address unless you provide them. This means allowing the access of a cookie doesn’t give them access to all of your data.

3.       itsaboutiphone.co.uk only uses cookies to personalize and secure your search experience. This is only to give you a personalized experience and retains your security without you watching security screen every time. The cookies are deleted upon your exit from the domain.

****1.9)** **Notices****

1.       The General Notices regarding our services are posted on itsaboutiphone.co.uk.

2.       All the outside events are beyond itsaboutiphone.co.uk domain’s control

3.       The website itsaboutiphone.co.uk is not liable for any delay in performance due to technical reasons. In such situation the obligatory conditions are thereafter beyond our control.

4.       We try our best to ensure your privacy at itsaboutiphone.co.uk. In this regard, you can be asked to identify yourself during you visit, the information you provide shall only be used for authentication purposes.

5.       itsaboutiphone.co.uk has the right to change its privacy policy at any given moment of time. Furthermore we shall not be liable to inform prior to changing our policy statement. However you shall be notified accordingly.

_This privacy policy statement is effective from May 2010._

## **Control you personal information**

If you differ from any of the above clause you can restrict yourself from sharing your personal information in the following ways

1)      When you are asked to fill in the form always check the box stating that you do not want to share the information with anyone else.

2)      itsaboutiphone.co.uk shall never sell or lease or distribute your personal information unless you gave the permission or is required by law to do so.

3)      You can always request your record of information we have in compliance with the Data Protection Act 1998

You agree that you have read the privacy policy of itsaboutiphone.co.uk and agree with the privacy policy and terms and conditions.

In regard to notices and general concerns you can always send your queries to [privacy@itsaboutiphone.co.uk](mailto:privacy@itsaboutiphone.co.uk)
